<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on ROB-IN Project</title>
    <link>https://projecte-robin.github.io/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on ROB-IN Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 21:29:20 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://projecte-robin.github.io/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Suara Caregivers Visit IRI</title>
      <link>https://projecte-robin.github.io/news/2022/02/17/workshop17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://projecte-robin.github.io/news/2022/02/17/workshop17/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday 17th, a group of professional caregivers from Suara visited the IRI laboratory to get to know the robots firsthand and be introduced to assistive robotics. During this visit, they were able to see the Tiago robot in action, navigating through the demonstrator flat or participating in cognitive games. After the visit, the Suara and IRI teams took part in an interdisciplinary working session to decide which tasks the robots could carry out to help the elderly and advance the three pillars of research that the ROB-IN project has as its flagship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kick Off!</title>
      <link>https://projecte-robin.github.io/news/2021/12/10/kickoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://projecte-robin.github.io/news/2021/12/10/kickoff/</guid>
      <description>On the 10th of December 2021, the kick-off meeting of the ROB-IN project took place at the premises of the Institute of Robotics and Industrial Informatics. Researchers from the different consortium members met to kick off the project and discuss the assistive tasks that the project robots were to perform during the pilots. The coordinators reviewed state of the art in assistive robotics over the last 15 years to assist in this exercise.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
